Shaked Elisha

949-466-4598 | elisha.shaked@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/shakedelisha

— Summary —

Graduated with a **Masters in Statistics, focused on Data Science, with a 3.5 GPA**. Experience in statistical planning, data analysis, and consulting. Ability to identify and solve problems resulting in structural improvements. Tenacity and drive to achieve goals, with a dedication and commitment consistent with organizational priorities. **Key strengths** include leadership, high sense of urgency, flexibility, proactive problem solving, self-motivated, detail oriented, analytical, interpersonal skills, and fluent written/verbal communications in three languages (English, French, and Hebrew).

Education

University of Pittsburgh

Pittsburgh, PA

Master of Arts in Statistics (3.5 GPA)

September 2018 - April 2019

<u>Relevant Courses:</u> Data Mining, Statistical Analysis and Optimization, Applied Multivariate Analysis, Survival Analysis, Python for Data Management and Analytics, Statistical Consulting.

Bachelor of Science in Statistics

September 2014 – April 2018

Minors: Economics, French

University Honors College, Emerging Leaders - Leadership Training, Completed Outside the Classroom Curriculum, Model UN, SEMF, Chabad, Sinai Scholars

<u>Relevant Courses:</u> Applied Regression with Written Component, Applied Time Series, Statistical Quality Control, Statistical Packages, Topics in Applied Statistics 1 (Data Science), Stochastic Processes, Intermediate Probability & Mathematical Statistics, Applied Statistical Methods 1 & 2 (graduate level course).

Technical Skills

Statistical Analysis: Data Mining, Data Munging, Data Management, Natural Language Processing, Data Visualization, Multivariate Analysis, Survival Analysis, Time Series Analysis, Stochastic Processes, Probability & Mathematical Statistics, Statistical Quality Control

Languages: R, LaTEX, SQL, Python, HTML, SAS

Software: Salesforce, Tableau, Minitab, Adobe Analytics, Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft Office Products (Excel, Word, PowerPoint, ...), IBM Rational DOORs

Languages: Fluent (speaking, reading, writing): English, French, Hebrew

Work History

Indegene Data Analyst

(Remote + Travel) Princeton, NJ December 2019 - Present

Analytics Lead for Adobe Support projects.

- Tracking team's work and deliverables, managing schedules and deadlines to dashboards and tag implementations
- Acting as point-of-contact for client relations and team communication
- DTM to Launch transition management
- Adobe Analytics support and training

Social Media sentiment identification

- Natural Language Processing training models to identify sentiment in social media posts
- Data set identification and munging
- Data Mining from unconventional sources

Model building for Categorization of text snippets

Natural Language Processing – for medical language

Support to Salesforce report and dashboard building, general use, and training creation

Medical Care Corporation

FAST Stage Prediction Consultant

Newport Beach, CA March 2019 – July 2019

Built a predictive model for the value of the MCIS test to FAST staging in Python and R

- Analyzed clinical datasets from patients diagnosed with dementia
- Patients took the "Mild Cognitive Impairment Screening" (MCIS) test of cognitive ability and were evaluated with the "Functional Assessment Staging Test" (FAST)

Built web applications using HTML to visualize the data.

<u>University of Pittsburgh – Department of Statistics</u> Statistical Consultant

Pittsburgh, PA

January 2019 – April 2019

Consulted on projects from clients affiliated the university.

- Clinical sample size calculations, clinical statistical analysis planning, big data inference, prediction, and identification of important variables, and multi-variable data visualization

University of Pittsburgh - Department of Statistics

Pittsburgh, PA

Statistics Computer Lab Student Worker

September 2018 – April 2019

Mentored and Tutored students of all levels in statistical concepts and programming.

<u> Johnson & Johnson – Cardiovascular Division</u>

Irvine, CA

Quality Systems Analyst Intern

May 2018 – July 2018

Provided data visualization for the Quality Systems Management Reports (QSMR). Led a project of optimizing the tracking and organization of external standards. Helped reformat quality plan for two companies (Biosense Webster and ASP).

<u>Johnson & Johnson – Biosense Webster</u> Quality Process and Engineering Intern

Irwindale, CA

June 2017 – August 2017

Led a project of identifying discrepancies in equipment data logs from an acquired company. Created a system to categorize and account for all incoming equipment. Logged incoming equipment into calibration record.

Johnson & Johnson - Biosense Webster

Irwindale, CA

RF Generator Product R&D Intern

June 2016 – May 2017

Defined Electro-Cardiology Therapeutic Ablation product requirements.

Worked with R&D teams in the US and Israel to collect requirements, align them in one delivery method, and integrate it into IBM Rational DOORs.

Reviewed, optimized, and performed quality analysis of R programs for code quality and performance.

Projects .

Music and Lyrical Data Analysis

2018

Musical data from Spotify's API and lyrics from Genius Lyrics' API using HTML scraping Stored in SQLite database using Python

Analysis done in R (sentiment analysis, high-dimensional linear regression, model selection techniques, regression and classification trees and ensembles, and neural network classification)

Volunteering

Chabad House on Campus – Jewish educational and religious community center for students (current) Challah for Hunger – food prep for donation

Assistant teacher to children's self-defense classes

Beach cleanups in Corona del Mar, Newport Beach